

SKILLS & CERTIFICATIONS

- · A+ (CompTIA)
- · Network+ (CompTIA)
- · Security+ (CompTIA)
- · Cloud+ (CompTIA)
- · Web Design
- Javascript
- · HTML5
- · CSS3
- . OOP
- · Git
- ·CLI · PHP
- · Laravel
- · Vue.js
- · React.is
- · Mobile software development
- · React Native
- · Python
- · mySQL
- · AWS · MongoDB
- · Agile methodologies
- · Scrum
- · Fluent Spanish
- · Fluent Italian
- · Certified notary public (FL)

LET'S CHAT:

+1-251-237-1222

7027 Chatum light run Bradenton, FL 34212

dcarrassi@outlook.com

Donato Carrassi

Junior Full Stack Developer/IT specialist

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

Demonstrated skill, consistency, and effort in a variety of roles performed as operational personnel in different industries - worked independently and in teams in the capacity of performing technical services on-demand. Participated in the release of a scalable solar proposal generation tool -- web application built with .vue and utilizing AWS. Developed a QuickBase CRM low code solution for roofing installers.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Web Developer

FREELANCE

OCTOBER 2020 - PRESENT

- https://www.solafide-services.com
- https://dc7-notes.netlifv.app
- https://myvanmyworld.netlify.app

Database Administrator/ Roofing specialist US ROOFING

APRIL 2020 - OCTOBER 2020

- · Developed a CRM on the Quickbase platform for US Roofing operations.
- · Maintained CRM and made modifications to specification.
- · Performed remote notary public duties and served as sales facilitator.

Project Manager/Solar specialist

US SOLAR

NOVEMBER 2018 - APRIL 2020

- · In house release of solar proposal tool (serverless web application).
- · Worked on React Native mobile application for solar monitoring.
- · Completed sales marks before expected timeframe consistently.
- · Onboarded, trained, and assisted new hires in the solar sales process.

Computer and phone repair technician

CPR CELLPHONE REPAIR/COMPUTER TROUBLESHOOTERS MAY 2018 - DECEMBER 2018

- · Tore down and re-assembled hundreds of devices during repair (laptops, desktop, and mobile) and troubleshooting.
- · Virus and malware removal along with systems optimization.
- · Provided on-site as well as remote support on demand.

EDUCATIONAL INFO

Hackademy Full Stack Developer Bootcamp

AULAB BARI

Completed 2021

Associates degree

STATE COLLEGE OF FLORIDA (SCF)

Completed 2019

Computer Programming and Analysis

Bachelors degree

UNIVERSITY OF CALIFORNIA: LOS ANGELES (UCLA)

Incomplete -- 70+ credit hours

Mechanical Engineering